Do they speak English?
I arrived in London at last.
The railway station was big, black and dark.
I did not know the way to my hotel, so I asked a porter.
I not only spoke English very carefully, but very clearly as well.
The porter, however, could not understand me.
I repeated my question several times and at last he understood.
He answered me, but he spoke neither slowly nor cle arly.
'I am a foreigner,' I said.
Then he spoke slowly, but I could not understand him.
My teacher never spoke English like that!
The porter and I looked at each other and smiled.
Then he said something and I understood it.
'You'll soon learn English!'
he said.
I wonder.
In England, each person speaks a different language.
The English understand each other, but I don't understand them!